
const STORE = [
	{ 
	  question: 'Which official has the final decision in matters of disputed goals?',
	  answers: [
	  'Video Goal Judge',
	  'Linesman', 
	  'Referee', 
	  'Goal Judge'],
	  correctAnswer: 'Referee'
	},
	{
	  question: 'A player is allowed to direct the puck to a teammate with an open hand, also known as a hand pass, if:',
	  answers: [
		'Both players are in their defensive zone',
		'Both players are in the neutral zone',
		'The pass originates in the defensive zone',
		'This is never allowed'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'Both players are in their defensive zone',
	},
	{
	  question: 'If a delayed penalty is signaled by the referee and the non-offending team subsequently ices the puck, where does the face off take place?',
	  answers: [
		'At the end face-off spot of the team icing the puck',
		'At center ice',
		'At the end zone face-off spot of the team who committed the penalty',
		'In the neutral zone near the defending blue line of the team icing the puck'
		],
		correctAnswer: 'In the neutral zone near the defending blue line of the team icing the puck',
	},
	{
	  question: 'In which of the following situations would a goal NOT be allowed?',
	  answers: [
		'When the puck is deflected directly into the net off a teammate',
	   'When the puck is deflected directly into the net off an official',
	  'When the puck is deflected directly into the net off a player of the opposing team',
	  'When the puck is deflected directly into the net off a dropped stick'
	  ],
	  correctAnswer: 'When the puck is deflected directly into the net off an official',
	},
	{
	  question: 'A goalkeeper is not allowed to participate in the play in any manner where?',
	  answers: [
		'Inside the face-off circles',
		'Beyond the blue line indicating his defensive zone',
		'Beyond the center red line',
		'Behind his own net'
		],
	  correctAnswer: 'Beyond the center red line',
	},
	{
	  question: 'The 12-inch wide blue lines are considered part of what zone?',
	  answers: [
		'Whatever zone the puck is in',
		'No man\'s land',
		'The end zones',
		'None - the line itself is separate from any zone'
		],
	  correctAnswer: 'Whatever zone the puck is in',
	},
	{
	  question: 'According to the USA Hockey Rule Book, what is the act of a player swinging his stick at an opponent, whether contact is made, or not?',
	  answers: [
		'Hooking',
		'Slashing',
		'Spearing',
		'Diving'
		],
	  correctAnswer: 'Slashing',
	},
	{
	  question: 'If a player prevents an opponent who has dropped his stick or any other piece of equipment from regaining possession of it, what is the proper penalty?',
	  answers: [
		'Unsportsmanlike conduct',
		'Interference',
		'Misconduct',
		'Holding'
		],
	  correctAnswer: 'Interference',
	},
	{
	  question: 'A team has two players serving penalties. A third player is subsequently called for a penalty. What happens?',
	  answers: [
		'The player goes to the penalty box, a substitute takes his place on the ice, and his penalty time begins immediately',
		'The player goes to the penalty box, a substitute takes his place on the ice, and his penalty time does not begin until one of the other penalties expires',
		'The player goes to the penalty box, the team\'s numerical strength is further reduced by one, and his penalty time begins immediately',
		'The other team is awarded a penalty shot'
		],
	  correctAnswer: 'The player goes to the penalty box, a substitute takes his place on the ice, and his penalty time does not begin until one of the other penalties expires',
	},
	{
	  question: 'The signal given for a misconduct penalty is:',
	  answers: [
		'Palm of hand on head',
		'Making a "T" sign with the hands',
		'Both hands on hips',
		'One arm raised'
		],
	  correctAnswer: 'Both hands on hips',
	},
	];